resume_pdf.md 4/21/2022

Jakub Szwajka

email: szwajkajakub@gmail.com

phone: +48 696 657 022

github: https://github.com/JakubSzwajka

linkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jakub-szwajka/

Dev.to: https://dev.to/kuba_szw

I am a programmer with three years of experience in building and maintaining apps within a different stacks. Starting from WordPress plugins, through SAP projects, ending with full-stack web development. I've managed to finish lots of projects as a team member and a few as a one-man army.

Django and React are my weapons of choice. I'm currently learning JS and Solidity a lot since I'm becoming a bigger and bigger fan of Web3.

Experience

August 2021 - present. TietoEvry

Software Engineer

- Implemented new features in fleet management web app with Django.
- Took active part in designing, reviewing, and refining new features.
- Worked with legacy code and made key components refactor to increase the speed of extending existing codebase.

Jun 2019 - present. BTech Sp. z o,o,

Python Developer

- Build a web platform using Django and React for managing notebook instances within the google cloud platform.
- Setting CI/CD pipeline using Docker, GitHub actions, and Cloud Build which lowered the feedback loop to minutes instead of hours.
- Redesigned app to work with a single instance instead of three, based on docker containers and Celery queues. This lowered costs of maintaining GCP instances significantly.
- Integrating the Django app with SAP for collecting data and building machine learning models to automate approval of purchase requisitions.
- Deployed Taiga software on AWS instance.

SAP ABAP Developer

- Made a program for controlling vendors against a white list of taxpayers. It was also the subject of my
 engineering thesis.
- Handled different bank web services in SAP reports.
- Made a desktop app with Java for digitally signing payment documents from SAP with XAdES standard.

resume_pdf.md 4/21/2022

• Standard enhancements using BTE in FI module for generating payment proposals.

Education

• WWSIS Horyzont. Engineering studies in the field of computer science September 2018 - March 2021

Other projects

- Car tracking and counting from a static camera using OpenCV only.
- 3D visualization of spinning donut using ASCII characters.
- Wordpress Website www.robertszwajka.pl End to end development and maintenance with lots of custom extensions using JavaScript
- Lots of algorithmic problems solved in Python and C++.
 - Traveling salesman problem with ant colony optimalization.
 - o Game of life problem.
 - Iterated prisoner dilemma problem.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).